<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://www.macktrucks.com/news-and-stories/press-releases/</id>
    <title>Mack News</title>
    <updated>1970-01-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>Mack News - Feed Generator</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.macktrucks.com/news-and-stories/press-releases/"/>
    <subtitle>Get the latest news from Mack® Trucks and see how we are taking our Born Ready semi truck line to the next level with new innovations and technology.</subtitle>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mack Trucks Features Mack Anthem® Models at TMC 2023 | Mack Trucks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macktrucks.com/mack-news/2023/mack-trucks-features-mack-anthem-models-at-tmc-2023</id>
        <link href="https://www.macktrucks.com/mack-news/2023/mack-trucks-features-mack-anthem-models-at-tmc-2023"/>
        <updated>1970-01-01T12:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[GREENSBORO, NC (Feb. 21, 2023) – Mack Trucks announced today that it will feature two versions of the Mack Anthem® model at the Technology & Maintenance Council’s (TMC) Annual Meeting. A Mack Anthem day cab and a Mack Anthem 70-inch stand-up sleeper will be in booth No. 1659 at TMC 2023, Feb. 27 – March 2, at the Orange County Convention Center, Orlando, Florida.]]></content>
        <published>1970-01-01T12:29:40.000Z</published>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mack Trucks Get a Digital Upgrade Industry-Leading Capabilities Now Available for More Systems | Mack Trucks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macktrucks.com/mack-news/2023/mack-trucks-get-a-digital-upgrade-industryleading-capabilities-now-available-for-more-systems</id>
        <link href="https://www.macktrucks.com/mack-news/2023/mack-trucks-get-a-digital-upgrade-industryleading-capabilities-now-available-for-more-systems"/>
        <updated>1970-01-01T12:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[ORLANDO, FL (Feb. 28, 2023) – Mack Trucks announced today that it will be expanding the number of electronic control units (ECUs) enabled for Mack® Over the Air (OTA) updates in the Mack Anthem®, PinnacleTM and Granite® models. The announcement was made at the Technology & Maintenance Council’s (TMC) 2023 Annual Meeting, Feb. 27 to March 2 at the Orange County Convention Center, Orlando, Florida.]]></content>
        <published>1970-01-01T12:29:45.000Z</published>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mack Defense Awarded a Contract for the Prototype and Testing Phase of U.S. Army’s Common Tactical Truck (CTT) Program | Mack Trucks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macktrucks.com/mack-news/2023/mack-defense-awarded-a-contract-for-the-prototype-and-testing-phase</id>
        <link href="https://www.macktrucks.com/mack-news/2023/mack-defense-awarded-a-contract-for-the-prototype-and-testing-phase"/>
        <updated>1970-01-01T12:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[ALLENTOWN, PA (Feb. 01, 2023) – Mack Defense has been awarded a contract to design, build, and deliver trucks for the prototype and testing phase of the U.S. Army’s Common Tactical Truck (CTT) program. The prototypes will be tested and evaluated to determine the final requirements for the next generation of trucks to ultimately begin modernization and replacement of the Army’s fleet of approximately 35,000 heavy tactical trucks which perform a wide range of combat logistics, support, and service support missions.]]></content>
        <published>1970-01-01T12:29:18.000Z</published>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mack Names Ballard Truck Center 2022 North American Dealer of the Year | Mack Trucks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.macktrucks.com/mack-news/2023/mack-names-ballard-truck-center-2022-north-american-dealer-of-the-year</id>
        <link href="https://www.macktrucks.com/mack-news/2023/mack-names-ballard-truck-center-2022-north-american-dealer-of-the-year"/>
        <updated>1970-01-01T12:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[GREENSBORO, NC (Feb. 14, 2023) – Ballard Truck Center of Tewksbury, Massachusetts, is the Mack Trucks 2022 North American Dealer of the Year. Mack named Ballard the winner during the recent Mack annual dealer meeting in Austin, Texas.]]></content>
        <published>1970-01-01T12:29:31.000Z</published>
    </entry>
</feed>